{
    "id": "ce6b51861e5e4d86997b643d5f33232e",
    "title": "Adjective or present participle",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "bfa74b3d510941cabb369b80c7a88784",
            "title": "Adjective Or Present Participle",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "A rolling stone gathers no moss.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Rolling is an adjective",
                        "Rolling is a present participle"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "That was an interesting book.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Interesting is an adjective",
                        "Interesting is a present participle"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "You are smoking too much.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Smoking is a present participle",
                        "Smoking is an adjective"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He put the smoking cigarette end in the ashtray.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Smoking is a present participle",
                        "Smoking is an adjective"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The delay was maddening.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Maddening is an adjective",
                        "Maddening is a present participle"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is waiting for us.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Waiting is an adjective",
                        "Waiting is a present participle"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The scenery was enchanting.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Enchanting is an adjective",
                        "Enchanting is a present participle"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Barking dogs seldom bite.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Barking is an adjective",
                        "Barking is a present participle"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The news was distressing.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Distressing is an adjective",
                        "Distressing is a present participle"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Interesting though it was, I didnâ€™t like the film.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Interesting is an adjective",
                        "Interesting is a present participle"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}